hi spring fans in this week's
嗨，本周的春季粉丝
installment of spring tips we're going
我们将要介绍的春季技巧
to look at how to demystify some of the
看一下如何揭开一些神秘的面纱
perceived magic and the typical spring
感知的魔法和典型的春天
boot application when I do talks people
当我说话时启动应用程序
wonder about some of these applications
想知道其中一些应用程序
I build especially in spring cloud world
我特别在春季云世界中建造
where a singl annotation switches on a
单个注解在
whole a whole barrage of functionality
整个功能弹幕
that whose implementation may not be
其实现可能不是
directly connected to annotation so what
直接连接到注解
I want to do is I want to explore just a
我想做的就是探索
little bit how spring boot in particular
一点点特别是弹簧靴
configures things for us and what you
为我们和您配置什么
can do to sort of pull back the veil and
可以做些拉回面纱和
understand what's happening in the
了解发生了什么事
background when you see some of these
当您看到其中一些背景时
things happening because at the end of
之所以发生，是因为
the day spring is just a configuration
春天只是配置
in application context in a
在应用程序上下文中
configuration container it's just a big
配置容器很大
bag of beans and everything that spring
一袋豆子和那春天的一切
does is just about managing these beans
要做的仅仅是管理这些bean
and these objects so let's go ahead and
这些对象，让我们继续前进，
build a typical example in the spring
在春天树立一个典型的例子
cloud world the config server right so
云世界的配置服务器，所以
I'm going to build a config service I
我要建立一个配置服务
build a config server I've got the web
建立一个配置服务器，我已经上网了
support there I don't need it ready and
支持那里，我不需要准备，
there's did generate now this config
现在确实生成了此配置
service let me try it again here we go
服务让我在这里再次尝试
this config service is a Springwood
此配置服务是Springwood
application and it's going to babysit a
应用程序，它将照看
directory full of configuration to the
充满配置的目录
example I was used for my for my example
我曾经为我的例子
here is this git repository and I'll
这是这个git存储库，我将
clone that to my directory here my
将其克隆到我的目录中
desktop config and in my my Springwood
桌面配置和我的Springwood
application i'll say spring that
我会说春天的申请
application dot name equals config -
应用程序点名称等于config-
service and i'll tell it where to find
服务，我会告诉它在哪里可以找到
the configuration which is the directory
配置是目录
we've just cloned the spring cloud
我们刚刚克隆了春天的云
config server get get dot uri equals
配置服务器获取获取点uri等于
home desktop config and finally I'll
家用桌面配置，最后我将
tell it to run import 8888 all right now
告诉它现在立即运行导入8888
for all that to have effect I need to
为了使所有效果生效，我需要
say at me will config server and then I
对我说将配置服务器，然后我
can run it I just hit command our
可以运行它，我只需点击命令我们
control our rather and it spins up a
控制我们，而是旋转一个
spindle ta instance inside of my IDE and
我的IDE中的主轴ta实例和
within a few seconds here I'll have I
几秒钟之内我就会
config server and I can confirm as much
配置服务器，我可以确认
by going to a local host 8080 8:00
通过访问本地主机8080 8:00
reservation I haven't service for such
我没有为这样的预订
default so you can see I've built a REST
默认，所以您可以看到我已经构建了REST
API it's ax it's babysitting you know
API是斧头，是保姆，你知道
mediating access to these configuration
调解对这些配置的访问
files and it's doing all this based on
文件，它基于
what this annotation and a pointer to
此注释和指向的指针
the directory where it should find the
应该在其中找到目录
configuration and so I can you know I
配置，所以我可以知道吗
understand the complaints that it's a
了解这是一个抱怨
little indirect it's not easy to sort of
间接的有点不容易
understand what just happened so let's
了解发生了什么，所以让我们
go ahead and take a moment to kind of
继续花一点时间
take a look at first of all spring boots
首先看一下春季靴子
Auto configuration mechanism when spring
弹簧自动配置机构
boot starts up it looks on the class
引导启动，它看起来像在课堂上
path for a text file called spring dot
称为弹簧点的文本文件的路径
factories it finds this text file in
工厂在其中找到此文本文件
various jars in particular for spring
各种罐子，特别是春天
boot it'll find a text file in spring
启动它会在春天找到一个文本文件
put Auto configure directory or a jar
把自动配置目录或罐子
rather in the meta info folder inside
而不是在meta info文件夹里面
that jar so when it finds that jar to
那个罐子，所以当它找到那个罐子
then find this this is a service loader
然后找到这是一个服务加载器
spring that factories is so it it's a
春天工厂就这样了
name and attribute mapped to Java
名称和属性映射到Java
configuration classes and different
配置类和不同
parts of spring use different you know
春天的部分使用不同，你知道
keys to determine which classes to load
确定要加载哪些类的键
spring boot in particular cares about
春季靴子特别在乎
the one that says org Spring Framework
一个说org Spring Framework的人
thought oh configure enable auto
想哦配置启用自动
configuration when spring boot starts up
弹簧启动启动时的配置
it tries to run every single one of
它尝试运行每个
these Java configuration classes all of
这些Java配置类
them that you see there and you can see
他们在那里看到，你可以看到
there's quite a lot right there's auto
有很多权利，有汽车
configuration here for Couchbase and
在此处配置Couchbase和
Cassandra and elastic search and MongoDB
Cassandra和弹性搜索以及MongoDB
and neo4j and WebSockets and hypermedia
和neo4j以及WebSockets和超媒体
and JMS and JTA and jane di and Davies
和JMS和JTA以及jane di和Davies
migrations and tax RS and security and I
移民和税收RS与安全以及我
mean just everything right all these
就是说一切都对
different things which may at first be a
不同的事物起初可能是
little off-putting we don't want all of
有点反感，我们不想全部
these to be running if we don't have the
如果我们没有这些就可以运行
libraries on the class person to support
图书馆对班上人的支持
them for example but spring will try
例如，但春天会尝试
in the mall so to kind of understand
在商场里，所以有点了解
what's happening let's take a look at
发生什么事让我们看一下
just a particular random all right you
只是一个随机的东西好吗
know auto-configuration in this case the
在这种情况下知道自动配置
or a rabbit in queue auto-configuration
或自动配置队列中的兔子
this is just a spring java configuration
这只是一个Spring Java配置
class so if you know about Springs Java
类，如果您了解Springs Java
configuration you know that
你知道的配置
configuration classes are just Java
配置类只是Java
configuration classes that can produce
可以产生的配置类
objects and the objects are produced
对象和对象产生
from bean provider methods B methods
从bean提供者方法B方法
that are annotated but at being this
被注释但在这个
configuration class has a few extra
配置类有一些额外的
annotations you may not recognize these
您可能无法识别的注释
are the conditional annotations here the
是这里的条件注释
conditional annotations were introduced
引入了条件注释
in spring 4 and there they are what
在春季4，那里是什么
power spring boot right there they're
动力弹簧靴就在那里
one of the things that make spring boot
春季靴子之一
possible it allows spring to
可能它允许弹簧
conditionally activate different objects
有条件地激活不同的对象
based on certain tests we've done this
根据某些测试，我们已经做到了
before we've had similar support for
在我们获得类似的支持之前
this you know sort of support for this
你知道这个的支持
with with profiles so in the past you
与个人资料一起使用，因此过去您
could use spring profiles to
可以使用弹簧轮廓来
conditionally activate certain certain
有条件地激活某些确定的
parts of the object graph but it was
对象图的一部分，但是
limited to the presence or lack of
限于存在或不存在
presence of that profile in spring 4
该轮廓在春季4中的存在
we've made generic that that conditional
我们已经使泛型条件
mechanism so now you can provide any
机制，现在您可以提供任何
arbitrary connect condition to
任意连接条件
conditionally activate a beam so here we
有条件地激活光束，所以在这里我们
have a condition that a condition that
有一个条件
says create this configuration class but
说创建此配置类，但
only so long as the type called a rabbit
只要那种叫兔子
template class is on the class path and
模板类在类路径上，
similarly create this configuration
类似地创建此配置
class only so long as the channel duck
班级只要通道鸭
class is on the class path you can see
班级在您可以看到的班级路径上
that in my IDE right now this is read so
现在在我的IDE中读取
these types are not on the class path
这些类型不在类路径上
thus when Springwood starts up all of
因此，当Springwood启动时，
this will be inert it won't it won't get
这将是惰性的，不会，不会得到
activated at all none of it will be
完全被激活
evaluated so this configuration is as
评估，因此此配置为
good as not present basically if it were
很好，因为基本上没有
to be present if we were to go to our
要出席我们要去的地方
maven build here we could add for
Maven构建在这里我们可以添加
example spring boot starter AMQP and
春季启动启动器示例AMQP和
when the crafts paths are just some of
当工艺路线只是其中的一部分
the types become available now these
这些类型现在可用
classes are going to be activated and
课程将被激活，
then spring will try and evaluate each
然后春天将尝试并评估每个
individual buna well in this case it's
在这种情况下很好的个人布纳
gonna create a connection factory to
将创建一个连接工厂
talk to rabbitmq this is the client-side
与rabbitmq交谈，这是客户端
middleware
中间件
that we can use to talk to a rabbi to
我们可以用来跟拉比说话
instance its gonna cry and try and
例如它会哭泣并尝试
create that being for us but it's only
为我们创造那种存在，但这仅仅是
going to do so if there is not already a
如果还没有
being of type connection factory in the
属于类型连接工厂
context somewhere right so this is a
正确的地方，所以这是一个
Spring Framework aim Coupee rabbit
Spring Framework瞄准Coupee兔子
rabbit connection connection factory if
兔子连接连接工厂如果
you have defined a bean somewhere else
您在其他地方定义了一个bean
in your own Java configuration for
在您自己的Java配置中
example here you know I'll leave
例子在这里，你知道我会离开
actually important thing that for you
对你来说实际上很重要的事情
free as an exercise for you but I said
免费为您做运动，但我说
suppose we had defined on beam my custom
假设我们已经定义了我的习惯
rabbit MQ connection factory suppose we
兔子MQ连接工厂假设我们
had defined on beam this beam would take
在光束上已经定义了
precedence spring would ignore this beam
优先弹簧将忽略此光束
here and this in this configuration
在这个配置中
class in general so we'd be able to
一般上课，这样我们就可以
override the object itself we'd be able
覆盖对象本身，我们将能够
to change the bit of functionality that
改变一些功能
gets used to connect to a connected to
习惯于连接到已连接到
RabbitMQ so you know we've added we fold
RabbitMQ，所以您知道我们添加了折叠
spring we want rabbitmq we've signaled
春天，我们要用rabbitmq发出信号
that by adding the spring boot starter
通过添加弹簧启动启动器
mqp support here on the classpath spring
mqp在classpath弹簧上的支持
boot started mqp
启动启动的mqp
you know mostly just brings in other
你知道大部分只是带来其他
libraries these starter dependencies in
将这些入门依赖库存储在
spring boot very rarely have any java
春季引导很少有任何java
code in them almost never in fact their
他们里面的代码几乎从来没有
primary function is to simply manage
主要功能是简单地管理
other libraries to bring them in for you
其他图书馆为您带来
so here we bring in the basic spring
所以在这里我们引入了基本的春天
boot starter the rabbit queue types and
启动启动程序Rabbit队列类型和
the spring messaging the auto
春天的消息自动
configuration code this class in
此类的配置代码
particular lives in one jar spring boot
特别生活在一个罐子的弹簧靴中
auto configure so there's you know
自动配置，所以你知道
dozens and dozens of different auto
数十种不同的汽车
configurations in the one spring boot
一个弹簧靴中的配置
main jar and different combinations of
主罐和不同的组合
libraries activate different Auto
库激活不同的自动
configurations in that one main spring
一个主弹簧中的配置
boot jar so here we've used the spring
靴子，所以我们在这里用了弹簧
boot starter and Coupee to light up or
启动启动器和Coupee点亮或
to toggle on or activate the
开启或激活
functionality in the rabbitmq auto
rabbitmq auto中的功能
configuration that's not to say that you
配置并不是说你
couldn't you know explicitly bring in
你不知道明确引入
spring boot starter and compete directly
Spring Boot Starter，直接竞争
or rather the dependencies in spring
或更确切地说是spring的依赖
boots started mqp directly so you could
靴子直接启动了mqp，因此您可以
bring these three libraries into your
将这三个库带入您的
code directly instead of using spring
直接编写代码，而不是使用spring
boot starter AMQP and you'd have exactly
启动启动器AMQP，您将拥有
the same effect
同样的效果
right you have exactly the same effect
对，你有完全一样的效果
as if you had used the spring boosters
好像你用过弹簧助推器
and could be so beware of that if you're
可能要当心，如果你是
not using starters but some things are
不使用启动器，但有些事情是
available and some things become active
可用，有些事情变得活跃
it might be because you've got a library
可能是因为您有图书馆
that activates a certain benefaction
激活一定的收益
ality which brings us to the next
将我们带入下一个世界
question
题
we know that spring boot has these
我们知道春季靴子有这些
conditions and that these conditions can
条件，这些条件可以
be used to conditionally activate them
用于有条件地激活它们
different parts of the Arctic raft we
北极筏的不同部分
know that these conditions are
知道这些条件是
specializations of this of the act
该行为的专业化
conditional annotation in spring 4 and
Spring 4中的条件注释和
that the add conditional annotation in
在其中添加条件注释
turn takes a condition object a
转一个条件对象
condition class literal reference that
条件类文字引用
in turn just provides some programmatic
反过来只是提供一些程序化
tested tests for anything attest that
经过测试的任何证明
there's another object on the in the
在中还有另一个对象
application context attests for the
应用程序上下文证明
presence of a certain property it tests
它测试的某个属性的存在
for for anything right it tests you know
对于任何正确的东西，它都会测试您知道的
is mercury in retrograde it doesn't
是汞逆行吗
matter it can you can you can
可以的可以的
programmatically describe it then you
以编程方式描述它，然后你
can test it and so that is part of the
可以测试它，所以这是
story how do you know which tests are
故事你怎么知道哪些测试
true or false which ones are active at
对或错在哪个活跃
any given point and for this we have the
任何给定的点，为此，我们有
debug option so if you pass if you
调试选项，如果您通过则
specify debug in your application of
在您的应用程序中指定调试
properties like this equals true or you
这样的属性等于true或您
specify it as a - - you know debug
将其指定为--您知道调试
equals true or even just debug equals
等于true甚至调试等于
true or if you specify it in your IDE
true或在IDE中指定
for example here in IntelliJ you can say
例如在IntelliJ中，您可以说
at enable debug output there's a
在启用调试输出中，有一个
checkbox there whatever you do the
复选框，无论您做什么
result will get you to a very useful
结果将使您受益匪浅
utility here let me comment out these
实用程序在这里让我注释掉这些
three bits because I don't need them the
三位，因为我不需要它们
result will get you a very useful
结果会给你一个非常有用的
utility that is to say it'll print out a
实用程序，它会打印出一个
an enumeration of all the different auto
所有不同汽车的枚举
configurations and the conditions that
配置和条件
have evaluated positive or negatively as
正面或负面评价为
well as the sort of unactive ones right
以及那种不活跃的权利
so let's go ahead and see the outcomes
所以让我们继续来看结果
of all the different conditions in the
在所有不同的条件
application so this is gonna tell you
应用程序，所以这会告诉你
all the things that
所有的东西
spring boot when it tried to start up
尝试启动时的弹簧启动
evaluated in order to arrive at a the
评估以得出
state that it's in when it when it's
声明它在何时，何时
running so let's see
运行，让我们看看
there we are so there are our conditions
我们在那里，所以我们有条件
and if you see the conditions here are
如果您看到这里的条件是
printed out in a convenient easy to sort
打印方便，易于分类
of read format in the console scrolling
控制台滚动中的读取格式
up here we can see the negative matches
在这里，我们可以看到负匹配
these are the tests that were attempted
这些是尝试过的测试
but did not match and you can see a
但不匹配，您会看到一个
breakdown of the class and then the
班级细分，然后
specific condition
具体条件
you know the annotation conditional and
您知道注释是有条件的，
the test that it was trying to run and
它试图运行的测试
then we can see up here the positive
那么我们可以在这里看到积极的
tests the ones that did match and I
测试确实匹配的那些，我
think these is this is usually far more
认为这些通常是更多
interesting so here we go the Auto
有趣，所以这里我们去自动
configuration port this says that we
配置端口，这说明我们
evaluated the candidate of whether a
评估候选人是否
being of type abstract audit listener
类型为抽象审核侦听器
was not available inside of the auto
在汽车内部不可用
configuration called audit Auto
配置称为audit Auto
configuration and thus the you know the
配置，因此您知道
beam provider or the configuration class
梁提供程序或配置类
on which that active annotation was
该活动注释所在的位置
present was activated so this is the you
目前已激活，所以这是你
know now we have an easy way to
知道现在我们有一个简单的方法
understand which pins are in play based
了解哪些引脚在起作用
on the auto configuration and which ones
在自动配置上以及哪些
are you know contributed throughout of
您是否知道整个
configuration that still doesn't
仍然没有的配置
entirely explain this this is an enable
完全解释这是一个使能
annotation and in spring since spring
注解和春天以来的春天
3.1 we've had at navel annotations that
3.1我们在肚脐注释中
are sort of the Java annotation
是Java注释的一种
configuration equivalent of the various
相当于各种配置
annotation - driven elements in the XML
XML中注释驱动的元素
and the old-style XML so for example if
和旧式XML，例如
you had transactions if you wanted to
如果您想进行交易
enable transaction management in the
在中启用交易管理
spring you could say TX : the annotation
春天，您可以说TX：注解
hydrogen driven in the XML and now
在XML中驱动氢，现在
there's at naval transaction management
有海军事务管理
for example well what's happening here
例如，好吧，这是怎么回事
is that when spring sees this annotation
是当spring看到这个注释时
and it sees that it has at import it'll
它看到它在导入时会
import the configuration class which it
导入它的配置类
needs to to you know to run and a lot of
需要您知道要运行，并且很多
times these imports just bring in a
这些进口只是带来了
relevant object and the relevant object
相关对象和相关对象
because it's now present in the
因为它现在存在于
application context
应用环境
then allows a auto-configuration
然后允许自动配置
condition to evaluate to true so the
条件评估为真，所以
rest of it gets triggered based on the
其余的则根据
other configuration sometimes the import
其他配置有时会导入
just the at enable just asserts that you
只是at enable断言您
are interested in opting into whatever
有兴趣选择任何东西
functionality you're trying to get to
您想要获得的功能
and you bring in a marker object or some
然后带上一个标记物或一些
sort of object that spring cares about
春天关心的一种物体
and if it's there then it's used to to
如果在那里，那么它习惯了
tell the config server you know to tell
告诉您知道的配置服务器
the auto configuration somewhere else
其他地方的自动配置
that it should activate the rest of the
它应该激活其余的
graph that's required to support that
支持该图
functionality and this is a very common
功能，这是很常见的
pattern so for example if you use spring
模式，例如，如果您使用弹簧
boots starter batch on the on Akaka that
在Akaka上启动启动程序批处理
that batch support still requires at an
批量支持仍然需要
able batch processing for example right
能够进行批处理的权利
this is just a stipulate that you want a
这只是您要
certain functionality in place so we've
某些功能到位，所以我们已经
looked now at Java configuration we've
现在看一下我们的Java配置
looked at Auto configuration we looked
看了我们看过的自动配置
at how you can override certain parts of
如何覆盖某些部分
the object graph at all times by
对象图始终
providing objects of well-known types
提供已知类型的对象
because remember the end of a spring is
因为记得春天的结束是
just a framework and spring spring you
只是一个框架而已
know you is open for extension but
知道你愿意扩展
closed for modification you can provide
已关闭，您可以提供修改
objects that are intended to be slotted
打算插入的对象
into the and as a cago of the machine so
并作为机器的货物
to speak and and spring will do the
说话，春天会做的
right thing on it with it based on its
基于它的正确的东西
type earlier we looked at how rabbit the
较早的类型，我们看着兔子
rabbit auto-configuration
兔子自动配置
made it dead simple to override are the
使它很容易被覆盖是
configuration for a connection factory
连接工厂的配置
by providing a replacement beam but
通过提供替换光束，
that's a little a little overkill isn't
有点过分不是
it that's like throwing the baby out
就像把婴儿扔出去
with the bathwater that's a whole lot of
大量的沐浴水
functionality here that I wouldn't have
这里我没有的功能
- wouldn't want to have to duplicate
-不想重复
just to tweak one little thing and so
只是为了调整一件事
thankfully we can we have a much easier
值得庆幸的是，我们可以轻松得多
an 11 ooh to pursue a much easier
11 ooh追求容易得多
channel by which we can customize the
我们可以通过其定制渠道
creation of this connection Factory and
创建此连接Factory和
that doesn't say we can provide
那不是说我们可以提供
properties you see spring boot has
您看到的Spring Boot具有的属性
another kind of component called a
另一种称为
configuration properties POJO so here's
配置属性POJO，所以这里是
a configuration properties object it's
一个配置属性对象
an annotation that signals to spring
发出弹簧信号的注释
that all properties that come from the
所有来自
environment be they from the application
从应用程序环境
of properties in the jar or from the
罐子或从
adjacent environment or
邻近环境或
environment variables are for the config
环境变量用于配置
from the config server from Jane di or
从Jane di的配置服务器或
whatever this this property these
无论这个属性这些
properties get mapped onto fields on
属性映射到上的字段
this podium so spring that rhythm cue at
春天登上领奖台
host spring that Reverend cued up port
主持人春天指出牧师暗示港口
spring that RabbitMQ that username that
春天那RabbitMQ那用户名
password but as cell that virtual host
密码，但作为该虚拟主机的单元格
etc etc etc so I could override the
等等等，所以我可以覆盖
default here these these values get
这些默认值在这里获得
overlaid onto these fields and then the
覆盖在这些字段上，然后
configuration can inject that
配置可以注入
configuration properties object and then
配置属性对象，然后
use that to sort of configure the
用它来配置
connection factory in this case if I
如果我在这种情况下连接工厂
wanted to point my RabbitMQ connection
想指出我的RabbitMQ连接
factory to a particular host I could use
工厂可以使用的特定主机
a configuration object to you know to
您知道的一个配置对象
resolve the host that the user has
解决用户拥有的主机
specified and this way I don't have to
指定，这样我就不必
override the whole connection factory
覆盖整个连接工厂
beam I can just I can just tailor that
我可以我只是可以裁缝
one part of the configuration so with
配置的一部分，因此
with properties and with the the smart
与属性和智能
application of Auto configuration and
自动配置和应用
the conditional annotations were able to
条件注释能够
change everything in the in the stack
更改堆栈中的所有内容
everything in the and the framework
框架中的所有内容
everything in the and the machine you
机器中的一切和您
have full control so with that I want to
有完全的控制权，所以我想
we'll wrap up by saying that spring
我们会说那春天结束
boots most powerful asset is it's a
靴子最强大的资产是
convenience and then how easy it makes
便利，然后它变得多么容易
it to to build simple applications
它来构建简单的应用程序
thanks for joining and I hope see you
感谢您的加入，希望您再见
next time
下次
you
您